Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one can stop us, we rise through the storm♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع إيقافنا، نحن ننهض من خلال العاصفة♪
♪Even bleeding and broken, we'll still push on♪
♪حتى مع النزيف والكسر، سنستمر في المضي قدمًا♪
♪The earth quakes with furious might♪
♪تهتز الأرض بقوة شديدة♪
♪I'll hold your hand and charge into the light♪
♪سأمسك بيدك وأتجه نحو النور♪
♪Adventurers, a new tale begins♪
♪المغامرون، تبدأ قصة جديدة♪
♪Brave hearts in the real world win♪
♪القلوب الشجاعة تفوز في العالم الحقيقي♪
♪Sparks fly when courage collides♪
♪تتطاير الشرر عندما تلتقي الشجاعة♪
♪Burning bright, our crystal tears ignite♪
♪تحترق بشدة، وتشتعل دموعنا البلورية♪
♪Above this city we stand tall♪
♪ فوق هذه المدينة نقف شامخين ♪
♪Flying wild, we're breaking every wall♪
♪نطير في البرية، ونكسر كل الجدران♪
♪Love's grand adventure, we'll conquer it all♪
♪مغامرة الحب الكبرى، سوف نتغلب عليها جميعًا♪
=Keeping Up with Beauty= (Adapted from "The Highborn Matron Reborn as the Pitiful Heiress")
=مواكبة الجمال= (مقتبس من "السيدة النبيلة التي ولدت من جديد وريثة بائسة")
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Did you get hurt?
هل تعرضت للأذى؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Find your phone and call the police first.
ابحث عن هاتفك واتصل بالشرطة أولاً.
Didn't expect you to know how to fight like that.
لم أتوقع أنك تعرف كيف تقاتل بهذه الطريقة.
I had no idea.
لم يكن لدي أي فكرة.
There are still many things you don't know.
لا يزال هناك الكثير من الأشياء التي لا تعرفها.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I'll try to know you better.
سأحاول أن أعرفك بشكل أفضل.
No battery.
لا يوجد بطارية.
Mine's dead too.
لقد مات لي أيضا.
We probably can't make it to the board meeting.
ربما لا نتمكن من حضور اجتماع مجلس الإدارة.
Let's head out first.
دعونا نخرج أولا.
Maybe we can still make it.
ربما لا زال بإمكاننا تحقيق ذلك.
Watch out!
احذر!
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
Gu Chenyu!
قو تشينيو!
Hang in there.
إصمد.
We'll get out first.
سنخرج أولا.
What time is it now?
ما هو الوقت الآن؟
Why isn't Gu Chenyu here yet?
لماذا لم يأتي Gu Chenyu إلى هنا بعد؟
How dare he be late on such an important day.
كيف يجرؤ على التأخر في مثل هذا اليوم المهم.
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Does he already think he'll be the new head of the Gu family?
هل يعتقد بالفعل أنه سيكون الرئيس الجديد لعائلة جو؟
Uncle.
عم.
No need to rush.
لا داعي للتسرع.
Let's wait a bit longer.
دعونا ننتظر لفترة أطول قليلا.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
The old madam woke up last night.
استيقظت السيدة العجوز الليلة الماضية.
After the doctor's diagnosis,
بعد تشخيص الطبيب،
her brain suffered irreversible damage.
لقد أصيب دماغها بأضرار لا يمكن إصلاحها.
She's showing signs of dementia
إنها تظهر عليها علامات الخرف
and she'll need long-term care in hospital.
وستحتاج إلى رعاية طويلة الأمد في المستشفى.
The Gu family needs a new head.
عائلة جو تحتاج إلى رئيس جديد.
The head of the Gu family isn't only the family leader,
رئيس عائلة جو ليس مجرد زعيم العائلة،
but also the president of Gu Group.
ولكن أيضًا رئيس مجموعة Gu.
It should be decided by shareholding ratio.
ينبغي أن يتم تحديد ذلك حسب نسبة المساهمة.
The old madam once signed a document.
لقد وقعت السيدة العجوز على وثيقة ذات مرة.
If one day she met with an accident
إذا تعرضت لحادث ذات يوم
and could no longer serve as the family head,
ولم يعد بإمكانه أن يخدم كرئيس للأسرة،
then her 32 percent share in Gu Group
ثم حصتها البالغة 32 بالمائة في مجموعة جو
would be divided in two,
سيتم تقسيمها إلى قسمين،
half to her grandson Gu Yansheng
النصف لحفيدها قو يان شنغ
and half to Gu Chenyu.
ونصف إلى Gu Chenyu.
Including this portion,
بما في ذلك هذا الجزء،
Gu Chenyu
قو تشينيو
would hold 35 percent of Gu Group,
سوف تمتلك 35 في المائة من مجموعة Gu،
making him the largest shareholder.
مما يجعله المساهم الأكبر.
Gu Yansheng
قو يانشنغ
would hold 26 percent,
سوف تمتلك 26 في المائة،
becoming the second largest shareholder.
لتصبح ثاني أكبر مساهم.
Therefore,
لذلك،
Gu Chenyu
قو تشينيو
shall be the next...
سيكون التالي...
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
So,
لذا،
the one holding the most shares now
الشخص الذي يحمل أكبر عدد من الأسهم الآن
will become
سوف تصبح
the next head of the Gu family?
الرئيس القادم لعائلة جو؟
According to tradition, yes.
وفقا للتقاليد، نعم.
After my husband passed away,
بعد وفاة زوجي،
I held 10 percent of the group's shares.
كنت أملك 10 بالمائة من أسهم المجموعة.
Now I
الان انا
voluntarily transfer these shares
نقل هذه الأسهم طواعية
(Gu Group Share Transfer Agreement) to my son, Gu Yansheng.
(اتفاقية نقل أسهم مجموعة جو) إلى ابني، جو يانشينغ.
Yansheng now holds over 36 percent of the company,
تمتلك شركة Yansheng الآن أكثر من 36 بالمائة من الشركة،
becoming the largest shareholder.
لتصبح أكبر مساهم.
Gu Yansheng
قو يانشنغ
is more qualified than Gu Chenyu to be the family head.
مؤهل أكثر من Gu Chenyu ليكون رئيسًا للعائلة.
Such an important matter,
مثل هذا الأمر مهم للغاية
since Gu Chenyu isn't here,
بما أن Gu Chenyu ليس هنا،
why don't we postpone it?
لماذا لا نؤجله؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
Everyone's time is precious.
وقت الجميع ثمين.
It's not easy to call a meeting.
ليس من السهل دعوة إلى اجتماع.
We can't just delay it.
لا يمكننا تأجيل الأمر فحسب.
Gu Chenyu isn't family head yet,
غو تشين يو ليس رئيسًا للعائلة بعد،
but he already ignores us.
لكنّه يتجاهلنا بالفعل.
Once he's in power,
بمجرد وصوله إلى السلطة،
he'll be even more arrogant.
سيكون أكثر غطرسة.
We better just choose Yansheng.
من الأفضل أن نختار Yansheng.
Agreed.
متفق.
Then...
ثم...
Thank you for your support, elders.
شكرا لدعمكم يا شيوخ.
Let's proceed with the vote.
دعونا ننتقل إلى التصويت.
Shareholders in favour of Gu Yansheng
المساهمون لصالح Gu Yansheng
becoming the new head of the Gu family,
أصبح الرئيس الجديد لعائلة جو،
please raise your hand.
من فضلك ارفع يدك.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Pulse is normal.
النبض طبيعي.
No major harm.
لا يوجد ضرر كبير.
Luckily this time the internal organs weren't pierced,
لحسن الحظ هذه المرة لم يتم ثقب الأعضاء الداخلية،
but you lost too much blood.
ولكنك فقدت الكثير من الدماء.
Your vital energy is severely depleted and need to rest.
لقد استنفدت طاقتك الحيوية بشكل كبير وتحتاج إلى الراحة.
However,
لكن،
why is your heart racing so fast?
لماذا قلبك ينبض بسرعة كبيرة؟
The blanket's too warm.
البطانية دافئة جدًا.
Shen,
شين،
at the board meeting,
في اجتماع مجلس الإدارة،
has Gu Yansheng already become family head?
هل أصبح Gu Yansheng بالفعل رئيسًا للعائلة؟
Except for Third Uncle and the two uncles,
باستثناء العم الثالث والعمَّين،
everyone else voted in favour.
صوت الجميع لصالح ذلك.
He bought off so many people,
لقد اشترى الكثير من الناس،
seems premeditated.
يبدو أنه متعمد.
My stepmother,
زوجة أبي،
for the sake of her own son,
من أجل ابنها،
really went to great lengths.
لقد ذهب إلى أطوال كبيرة حقا.
It's a pity those bandits got away.
من المؤسف أن هؤلاء اللصوص تمكنوا من الفرار.
Now there's no evidence to prove
الآن لا يوجد دليل لإثبات ذلك
these matters are connected to Bai Lanxing and Gu Yansheng.
ترتبط هذه الأمور بباي لانشينغ وغو يانشينغ.
Shen,
شين،
thank you for today.
شكرا لك على اليوم.
If you hadn't arrived in time,
إذا لم تصل في الوقت المناسب،
things would have been dire.
لقد كان الأمر ليكون خطيرا.
It wasn't me.
لم أكن أنا.
Yunyun.
يونيون.
Flowers suit the beauty.
الزهور تناسب الجمال.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank...
شكر...
Stabbed and still so spirited.
طعنت ومازالت قوية.
Mr. Gu really is tough.
السيد جو صعب حقا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I need to rest.
أحتاج إلى الراحة.
See the guests out.
انظر إلى الضيوف.
You treat
انت تعالج
your lifesaver like this?
هل هذا هو منقذ حياتك؟
He… He saved me?
هو... هو أنقذني؟
Gu Chenyu, hold on.
غو تشينيو، انتظر.
I'll take you to hospital right away.
سأأخذك إلى المستشفى على الفور.
Anyone here?
هل يوجد أحد هنا؟
Yunyun.
يونيون.
Come.
يأتي.
Luckily Yunyun shared her location with me.
لحسن الحظ أن يونيون شاركت موقعها معي.
I saw her position moving into a remote area.
لقد رأيت موقعها يتحرك إلى منطقة نائية.
I guessed she was in trouble.
ظننت أنها كانت في ورطة.
Actually, it was quite dangerous.
في الواقع، كان الأمر خطيرًا جدًا.
Thanks for helping out.
شكرا لمساعدتك.
No need to mention it.
لا داعي لذكر ذلك.
As long as it's to see you,
طالما أن الأمر يتعلق برؤيتك،
I'd go through fire and water.
سأمر عبر النار والماء.
Thirsty.
عطشان.
Gu Chenyu,
قو تشينيو,
you should thank him too.
ينبغي عليك أن تشكره أيضاً.
He saved your life.
لقد أنقذ حياتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
I was looking for Yunyun.
كنت أبحث عن يونيون.
You just happened to be along the way.
لقد حدث أنك كنت على طول الطريق.
Don't be too moved.
لا تتأثر كثيرا.
We're family after all.
نحن عائلة بعد كل شيء.
Helping her is helping me.
مساعدتها هي مساعدتي.
Then I won't disturb Mr. Gu's rest.
ثم لن أزعج راحة السيد جو.
After all that trouble,
بعد كل تلك المتاعب،
you look worn out.
تبدو مرهقًا.
You should take care of yourself as you age.
يجب عليك الاعتناء بنفسك مع تقدمك في السن.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you'll age faster.
سوف تكبر بشكل أسرع.
I'll walk you out.
سأخرجك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Otherwise, you'll age faster.
وإلا فسوف تكبر أسرع.
Do I...
هل انا...
Do I look worn out?
هل أبدو مرهقًا؟
♪Words I can't say linger on my tongue♪
♪الكلمات التي لا أستطيع قولها تبقى على لساني♪
♪Each time you're near, my heartbeat runs♪
♪في كل مرة تكون بالقرب، ينبض قلبي♪
♪Cold nights glow with gentle stars above♪
♪الليالي الباردة تتوهج بالنجوم اللطيفة في الأعلى♪
♪My silent thoughts stretch long like dreams of love♪
♪أفكاري الصامتة تمتد طويلاً مثل أحلام الحب♪
♪How do I hide these feelings so faint and shy♪
♪كيف أخفي هذه المشاعر بهذا القدر من الخجل والضعف♪
♪When I meet you again, warmth flows quietly by♪
♪عندما ألتقي بك مرة أخرى، يتدفق الدفء بهدوء♪
♪My eyes can't help but turn your way♪
♪لا يمكن لعيني إلا أن تتجه نحوك♪
♪I close them tight, pretending all is the same♪
♪أغلقهم بإحكام، وأتظاهر بأن كل شيء متشابه♪
♪The wind brushes softly by♪
♪تمر الرياح برفق♪
♪Carrying half of my sigh♪
♪أحمل نصف تنهيدة♪
♪I walk a while, then glance behind♪
♪أمشي لفترة، ثم أنظر خلفي♪
♪You bring back warmth I thought I'd lost♪
♪لقد أعادت لي الدفء الذي اعتقدت أنني فقدته♪
♪My pain quietly thaws♪
♪يذوب ألمي بهدوء♪
♪And in silence, loneliness fades away♪
♪وفي الصمت يتلاشى الشعور بالوحدة♪
♪Because you are my light in the dark♪
♪لأنك نوري في الظلام♪
♪I'll be your sun when winter feels too hard♪
♪سأكون شمسك عندما يصبح الشتاء قاسيًا جدًا♪
♪We shine for each other through the quiet and the loneliness♪
♪نحن نتألق لبعضنا البعض من خلال الهدوء والوحدة♪
♪You are the warmest light in all my world♪
♪أنت أدفأ ضوء في عالمي كله♪